ellie.com 2015-03-25

# Luxury Workout and Activewear for Women | Exercise Apparel | Ellie

Ellie Fashion Group, Inc. (“Ellie Fashion Group”, “ELLIE”, “We”, “Us” or “ Our”) values your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. Ellie Fashion Group is an online service that delivers high-quality women’s activewear and accessories to its subscription members once a month (“Services”). Ellie Fashion Group is also an ecommerce site located at http://www.ellie.com (the “Site”), with items available for purchase on our storefront at stated retail pricing (also part of the “Services”).

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how and when ELLIE collects, uses and shares your information when you use our Services or Site. By using Our Site and/or purchasing a FFC (Fit Fashionista Club) Membership you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorize ELLIE to use your information in the United States and any other country where ELLIE operates for the purposes set forth in this Policy. This Policy is incorporated by reference into the Ellie Fashion Group Terms of Service. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact customer service.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

The information We collect from you enables us to fulfill your request for our products you order and receive, to send you information or content in which you may be interested, and keep you abreast of any updates related to our Site and/or your Membership. We also use this information to personalize and continually improve our Site, your experience, and to ultimately serve you better. When we reference personal information in this Policy, we mean information hat allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data

Information Collected Upon Registration: You may browse our Site without registering. If you would like to place an order, become an FFC member, and/or request information from us then we require you to register with us and become a member on our Sites. When you create, register, or edit your ELLIE account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, email address, and password. Please safeguard your password and other personal information.

Other Information We Collect About You as You Use the Site: In some circumstances, such as making a purchase of our products, we will request that you provide your credit card, debit card, or acceptable payment option and your billing address and shipping address. You are welcome to not provide this information, but if you do not wish to provide this information then there is no way for us to ship you our products. When you post messages on the message boards of our Site, the information contained in your posting will be stored on our servers and other users will be able to see it. We also collect other types of personal information that you provide to us voluntarily as you use the Site or Services or if you contact us via e-mail regarding the Services. 

If you participate in a sweepstakes, contest or giveaway on our Site, we may ask you for your e-mail address and/or home number (to notify you if you win or not). We may also ask for first and last names, and sometimes post office addresses to verify your identity. In some situations we may need additional information as a part of the entry process, such as a prize selection choice. These sweepstakes and contests are voluntary. We recommend that you read the rules for each sweepstakes and contest that you enter.

Information that We Collect About You from Facebook: You may also log-in to our Site using your Facebook account. Facebook controls the information collected from you during the log-in process; ELLIE does not control the information that Facebook collects from you. If you log-in to our Site using Facebook, you must enter your Facebook email address and password. We will also ask that you grant us permission to (i) access and collect your Facebook basic information (this includes your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user IDs, list of friends, date of birth, email address, and any other information you have you have set to public on your Facebook account); (ii) send you email; (iii) post to your Wall; (iv) access posts in your news feed; and (v) access your Facebook data at any time even if you are not using Facebook. Please note if you allow ELLIE to have access to this information, then ELLIE will have access to this information even if you have chosen not to make that information public. For information about how Facebook may disclose your information, including any information you make public, please consult the Facebook Privacy Policy. We have no control over how Facebook uses or discloses the personal information you provide to it. We store the information that we receive from Facebook along with other information that we collect from you or receive about you and consider it to be personal information of you.

INFORMATION USE

We will use your personal information to:

  * Provide you with Services and customer support and fulfill your orders;
  * Market our products and services to you that we believe may be of interest to you;
  * Respond to your requests, resolve disputes and/or troubleshoot problems;
  * Improve the quality of the Sites and the Services; and 
  * Communicate with you about the Sites and the Services.

We may also use your Personal Information to create Anonymous Information records by excluding information that makes the information personally identifiable to you.

We will communicate with you primarily in the form of emails. You can manage the frequency and/or opt out of receiving these communications by changing your settings on the Site and/or clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email. Please note that even if you unsubscribe or opt-out, we may still send you Site and Services related communications (e.g., emails related to your account or the Site).

Information We Collect Automatically: In addition, when you visit the Sites and/or register for Membership, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons, and other automated devices. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor‘s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server. We also may use third-party website analytics tools (such as Omniture, Google Analytics, and Facebook Insights), that collect information about visitor traffic on the Sites. The information we or they may collect by automated means includes:

  * Information about the devices our visitors use to access the Internet (such as the IP address and the device, browser, domain name and operating system type)
  * URLs that refer visitors to our sites
  * Dates and times of visits to our sites
  * Information on actions taken on our sites (such as page views and site navigation patterns)
  * A general geographic location (such as country and city) from which a visitor accesses our websites
  * Search terms that visitors use to reach our sites and the webpage that led you to the Sites

Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Site, rather than your name or other personally identifying information. We do not combine the information generated through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Although Google Analytics plants a persistent Cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the Site, the Cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.

COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGY:

Cookies Information: Cookies are small pieces of information which are issued to your computer when you visit a website and which store and sometimes track information about your use of the Service. ELLIE uses cookies to help recognize you as a repeat visitor, to improve the quality of our Service, and to try and make your browsing experience meaningful. When you enter our Sites, our web server sends a cookie to your computer which allows us to recognize your computer but not specifically who is using it. By associating the identification numbers in the cookies with other customer information when, for example, you log-in to the Service, then we know that the cookie information relates to you. Some of the cookies used by our site are served by us, and some are served by third parties who are delivering services on our behalf. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set. You can also learn more about cookies by visitingwww.allaboutcookies.org which includes additional useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different browsers. By blocking or deleting cookies used on our Service, you may not be able to take full advantage of our Service.

Log File Information or Log Data: Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, interact with our email notifications, or visit a third-party website that includes a ELLIE button or widget. ELLIE uses Log Data to provide our Services and to measure, customize, and improve them. If not already done earlier, we will either delete Log Data or remove any common account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 18 months, except as otherwise required by law.

Links: ELLIE may keep track of how you interact with links across our Services, including our email notifications, third-party services, and client applications, by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, to provide more relevant advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

We do not disclose your personal information except in the limited circumstances described here.

Your Consent: We may share or disclose your information at your direction, such as when you authorize a third-party web client or application as log-in credentials when you register for Membership. 

Service Providers: We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us in the United States and abroad. 

Law and Harm: Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect ELLIE's rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information.

Affiliates: We may share some or all of your personal information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (“Affiliates”), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Policy. 

Business Transfers: We may share some or all of your personal information in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, personal information may also be transferred as a business asset. If another company acquires our company, business, or assets, that company will possess the personal information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Policy.

Social Networking Sites. Some of our Services may enable you to post content to SNSs (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). If you choose to do this, we will provide information to such SNSs in accordance with your elections. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for your use of those websites and that it is your responsibility to review the terms of use and privacy policy of the third party provider of such SNSs. We will not be responsible or liable for: (i) the availability or accuracy of such SNSs; (ii) the content, products or services on or availability of such SNSs; or (iii) your use of any such SNSs.

HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on Our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented help reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions, including, where appropriate, password protection, encryption, SSL, firewalls, and internal restrictions on who may access data to protect our Site and the information We collect from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, signing off after using a shared computer, choosing a password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your password private. Also, you should never share your log-in information with others. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity. To change your Facebook password, you must go to the Facebook site and follow its procedures for changing your password.

MODIFYING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may modify any personal information that you have submitted by logging into your account and updating your profile information. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site for a period of time. If you would like to access or modify your Facebook profile information, or adjust the types of information we receive from Facebook, you must adjust your Facebook account settings directly through Facebook. We have no control over how Facebook shares your information with us or other third parties and changing your information on the Site does not change any information on Facebook. The information you provide to Facebook is subject to the Facebook Privacy Policy. 

OUR POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at customer service. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If a child under 13 submits personal information to us and we learn that such information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible

THIRD PARTY SITES

Our Site may contain links to third party websites. When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal information or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of your Personal information after you click on links to such outside websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website you visit. The links to third party websites or locations are for your convenience and do not signify our endorsement of such third parties or their products, content or websites.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at www.ellie.com. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
